<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kcolorchooser.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KColorChooser</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKColorChooserxx</name>
  <summary>Color selector and palette editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Selector de color i editor de la paleta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Selector de color i editor de la paleta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Colour selector and palette editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Selector de colores y editor de paletas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Selector de cores e editor de paletas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Kleurenkiezer en paletbewerker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Selector de cores e editor de paletas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Výber farby a editor palety</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Засіб вибору кольорів та редактор палітр</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxColor selector and palette editorxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
        KColorChooser is a color palette tool, used to mix colors and create custom
        color palettes.  Using the dropper, it can obtain the color of any pixel on
        the screen. A number of common color palettes are included, such as the standard Web colors
        and the Oxygen color scheme.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KColorChooser és una eina de paleta de colors, usada per barrejar colors i crear paletes color personalitzades. Usant el deixar anar, pot obtenir el color de qualsevol píxel de la pantalla. S'inclouen diverses paletes de color normals, com els colors estàndard Web i l'esquema de color Oxygen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KColorChooser és una eina de paleta de colors, usada per barrejar colors i crear paletes color personalitzades. Usant el deixar anar, pot obtindre el color de qualsevol píxel de la pantalla. S'inclouen diverses paletes de color normals, com els colors estàndard Web i l'esquema de color Oxygen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KColorChooser is a colour palette tool, used to mix colours and create custom colour palettes. Using the dropper, it can obtain the colour of any pixel on the screen. A number of common colour palettes are included, such as the standard Web colours and the Oxygen colour scheme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KColorChooser es una herramienta de paletas de colores que se usa para mezclar colores y crear paletas de colores personalizados. Puede obtener el color de cualquier píxel de la pantalla usando el cuentagotas. Se incluyen varias paletas de colores comunes, como los colores Web estándares y el esquema de colores Oxígeno.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KColorChooser é unha ferramenta de paleta de cores que se usa para mesturar cores e crear paletas de cores personalizadas. Pode usar o contagotas para obter a cor de calquera píxel da pantalla. Inclúense varias paletas de cores comúns, como as cores web estándar e o esquema de cores de Oxygen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KColorChooser is een hulpmiddel voor kleurpaletten, gebruikt om kleuren te mengen en aangepaste kleurpaletten. Met de dropper kan het de kleur van elk pixel op het scherm verkrijgen. Een aantal algemene kleurpaletten zijn meegekomen, zoals de standaard webkleuren en het Oxygen kleurschema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KColorChooser é uma ferramenta de paleta de cores, sendo usada para misturar cores e para criar paletas de cores personalizadas. Usando o conta-gotas, poderá obter a cor de qualquer ponto no ecrã. Está incluído um conjunto de paletas de cores comuns, como as cores-padrão da Web ou o esquema de cores Oxygen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KColorChooser — інструмент для роботи з палітрами, яким можна скористатися для змішування кольорів і створення нетипових палітр кольорів. За допомогою піпетки програма може отримувати колір з будь-якого пікселя екрана. До складу пакунка включено декілька типових палітр, зокрема стандартні кольори інтернету та кольори теми Oxygen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKColorChooser is a color palette tool, used to mix colors and create custom color palettes. Using the dropper, it can obtain the color of any pixel on the screen. A number of common color palettes are included, such as the standard Web colors and the Oxygen color scheme.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://kde.org/applications/graphics/kcolorchooser/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kcolorchooser</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kcolorchooser&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kcolorchooser/kcolorchooser.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kcolorchooser</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kcolorchooser.desktop</launchable>
</component>
